<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Apistear</string>
    <string name="juegos">Games</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">About</string>
    <string name="agregar">Add</string>
    <string name="continuar">Continue</string>
    <string name="NombresRepetidos">Please, don\'t repeat names</string>
    <string name="NoNombres">You need to type at least two names</string>
    <string name="UnNombre">Type more than one name, don\'t be a Forever Alone</string>
    <string name="jugador">Player</string>

    <!-- Copa del rey -->
    <string name="copa_del_rey">King\'s Cup</string>
    <string name="copareyAs">WATERFALL</string>
    <string name="coparey2">2 FOR U.</string>
    <string name="coparey3">3 FOR ME</string>
    <string name="coparey4">4 ON THE FLOOR</string>
    <string name="coparey5">5 FOR GUYS</string>
    <string name="coparey6">6 FOR CHICKS</string>
    <string name="coparey7">7 HEAVEN</string>
    <string name="coparey8">8 WITH MATE</string>
    <string name="coparey9">9 RHYME</string>
    <string name="coparey10">CATEGORIES</string>
    <string name="copareyj">MAKE A RULE</string>
    <string name="copareyq">QUESTION MASTER</string>
    <string name="copareyk">KING\'S CUP!!!</string>
    <string name="copareyReglas">
         King\'s cup is a drinking game that uses playing cards is this ccase, Apistear App ;) . The player must drink and dispense drinks based on cards drawn.
        Each card has a rule that is predetermined before the game starts. Many houses have their own variation of rules.\n

        Ace: \nAce is waterfall. This starts with everyone chugging.
        Then the person who picked the card can stop whenever he/she wants.
        This allows the next person to stop when he/she wants and so on and so on.
        This version is classic because it does a great job of getting everyone plastered.
        \nTwo:\n Two has and always will be the classic you.
        This means that whoever picks the 2 card gets to choose anybody they want in the game to drink.
        \nThree:\nThree for me. Pick a 3 and you have to drink.
        \nFour:\nFour on the floor, everybody has to point to the ground the last person to do it has to drink.
        \nFive:\n Five for guys. Guys have to drink.

        \nSix:\n Six for Chicks, girls have to drink.
        \nSeven:\nSeven heaven. All players reach for the sky.
             The last person has to drink. Great card when people aren\'t paying attention or someone is too
            drunk to realize a seven was picked.
        \nEight:\nEight is mate. The player who picks the card chooses another player to be their mate.
            This means when one of them drinks they both drink. Perfect for letting the fine girl across
            the table know you are interested.
        \nNine:\nNine is called bust a rhyme. The simple version has the player who picked the card say a
            word and everybody has to say a word that rhymes with it. Say for example the word is bite.
            Other players would say fight, kite, tight, right, etc. This goes on until somebody cannot
            think of a word that rhymes.

        \nTen:\nTen is categories. The player who picked the card chooses a category.
            Then everyone goes around and says something that fits in the category.
            Whoever cannot think of anything in the category has to drink.

            \nJack:\nMake a Rule. Player makes a rule that lasts the entire game and if broken the violator must drink
        \nQueen:\nQuestion Master.Player who flips over a queen becomes the question master until the next queen is flipped over.
            This player can ask anybody at any time a question and if that player doesn\'t respond with
            a question to the asker or another player he must drink

        \nKing:\nKing\'s Cup.Pour however much beer/liquor you want into the glass, the 4th king has to drink the cup.
    </string>

</resources>